(Sheldon:)What is it now, Mrs. Wolowitz?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)It's this dress.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)When I put my front in,
my back pops out.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)When I put my back in,
my front pops out.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)It's like trying to keep two dogs
in a bathtub.
(Sheldon:)What do you want me to do?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)We're gonna have to work as a team.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Get in here, grab a handful,
and start stuffing.
(Sheldon(off):)I'm not sure how to do this.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)It's easy. Just pretend
you're putting away a sleeping bag.
(Sheldon(off):)Sleeping bags don't usually
sweat this much, but okay.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Now zip me up.
(Sheldon(off):)Oh, if we squeeze you any tighter,
you might turn into a diamond.